一切都很美味  亲爱的
Everything was delicious, sweetie.
谢谢  宝贝
Thanks, baby.
工作如何
So, how was work?
缓慢而痛苦
Slow and painful.
一如既往
Same as always.
但是我被提升为值班主管了
Except for when I got promoted to shift supervisor.
我就知道
I knew it.
我们需要庆祝
We need to celebrate.
你有什么好主意吗
Do you have anything in mind?
其实呢...
As a matter of fact...
去开始吧  我收拾好这里
Go on, get things started. I'll clean up in here.
你确定吗
You sure?
当然  亲爱的
Of course, baby.
她真美  对吧
She's a beauty, isn't she?
好吧  等一下
All right, one second.
我不想弄脏衣服
Don't want to make a mess.
求你了
Please.
求你  求你了
Please. Please.
求你  不要
Please, don't.
不要
No!
黑吃黑
第四季
第四集
三个月前
轻点
Easy.
我救了你的命  不用谢
You're welcome for saving your life.
是我先救的你
Only after I saved yours.
怎么了
What?
你在这里做什么
What are you doing here?
我在帮你
I'm trying to help you.
不  我不是这个意思
No, that's not what I mean.
你在做什么
What are you doing?
必需做的事
What I have to.
别
No.
别跟我胡扯
That's bullshit.
你不用这样生活的
You don't have to live like this.
我该怎么做
What am I supposed to do?
跟你一样找个没人的地方躲起来吗
Hide away from the world like you?
不  你不用跟我一样
No, you don't do what I do.
你可以走
You can leave.
大千世界  去哪都行
There's a whole world out there.
你选择的生活
The life that you're choosing,
只会一个结果
it ends one way.
可能吧
Maybe.
但至少是我自己的选择
But at least it's my choice.
天啊
Jesus Christ.
你得离开
I need you to leave.
你得走
I need you to go.
-不  -走...
- No. - Get out of--
不要
Don't.
你知道丽贝卡·鲍曼怀孕了吗
Did you know that Rebecca Bowman was pregnant?
你已经问过我三次了
You've asked me that three times already.
我要问到我满意为止
And I'm gonna keep asking it till I'm satisfied.
你知道吗
Did you know?
不知道
No.
告诉我你跟丽贝卡的恋情
Tell me about your relationship with Rebecca.
我们没有恋情
It wasn't a relationship.
那是什么
Then what was it?
一直做炮友  直到你杀了她
Like just friends with benefits or something until you killed her?
-去你妈  布洛克  -去你妈
- Fuck you, Brock. - No, fuck you.
听着  我不觉得姑娘们是你杀的
Look, I don't think you're killing young girls.
但我不确定
But I don't know that you're not.
我只知道
The only thing I know is
自从你到了女妖镇  就一直在骗我
you've been lying to me since you got to Banshee.
谎言到此为止
And the lies end here.
你上次见到她是什么时候
When was the last time you saw her alive?
我不知道  有一阵子了
I don't know. A while ago.
你得说得更详细点
I need you to be more specific than that.
我他妈又不写日记
I don't keep a fucking diary.
她车的GPS定位显示
Her car's GPS proves
她被杀那天晚上去了你的住处
she was at your cabin the night she was killed.
-我说过了  我没见到她  -真的吗
- Like I told you, I didn't see her. - Really?
你怎么会记得  你他妈又不写日记
How do you know? I mean, you don't keep a fucking diary.
我认为你那晚见到她了
I think you did see her that night.
我认为她告诉你她怀孕了
I think she told you she was pregnant.
我了解你  你或许无法接受这个事实
Knowing you, you probably didn't take that news too well,
你们吵了起来
so you argued.
也许后来打起来了
Maybe it turned violent, physical.
没有
No.
为什么她车里有你的血
Why is your blood in her car?
我不知道  你怎么不去问问普罗科特
I don't know. Why don't you ask Proctor?
-我在问你  -我不记得了
- I'm asking you. - Well, I don't remember.
那你记不记得
Well, do you remember
把这两个女孩的心脏挖出来的事
cutting the hearts out of these two girls?
天哪  别这样  你了解我的  布罗克
Jesus Christ. Come on, you know me, Brock.
不  不是这样  我不了解你
No, see, I don't. I don't know you.
我只知道
The only thing I know is that
西沃恩被杀后  你陷入了深渊
you went off the deep end when Siobhan was killed.
你崩溃了  也许你像个精神病一样
You snapped and maybe you're reenacting her death
一次又一次地重温她的死状
over and over and over again like some psychotic--
天哪  你他妈睁眼看看  布罗克
Jesus, open your fucking eyes, Brock!
这不是冲动犯罪
This didn't happen in the moment.
不管是谁干的  都有详细计划
Whoever did this shit took time to plan it!
你想啊
Think!
怎么  你觉得我让她们也怀孕了
What, you think I got them pregnant as well?
你他妈的知道不是我干的
You fucking know it wasn't me.
我什么都不知道
I don't know anything!
是啊  差不多吧
Yeah, well, that about sums it up.
泰德  谢里尔  马丁  你们今早过得好吗
Ted, Sheryl, and Martin. How y'all doing this morning?
请坐  沃茨先生
Have a seat, Mr. Watts.
报上姓名  以供记录
State your name for the record.
兰道尔·科迪·沃茨
Randall Cody Watts.
早安  沃茨先生  我是泰德·史密斯委员
Good morning, Mr. Watts. I'm Commissioner Ted Smith.
跟我一起来的是谢里尔·戈登委员
I'm joined today by Commissioner Sheryl Golden
和马丁·戴维斯委员
and Commissioner Martin Davis.
我们都见过
Yeah, we've all met.
今天是你...
Today is your...
第六次会见假释委员会
sixth appearance before this board of parole.
说是就是吧  泰迪  我记不清了
If you say so, Teddy. I've lost count.
谢里尔  我看你终于怀上了
Sheryl, I see you finally had that baby.
是的
I did.
希望你和戈登先生挑了个不错的英国名
I hope you and Mr. Golden picked out a nice Anglo name.
沃茨先生  建议你严肃对待本次听证
Mr. Watts, I suggest you take this hearing seriously.
你旁边那个犹太佬呢
What about the kike sitting next to you?
你觉得她严肃对待了吗
You think she's taking this seriously?
-沃茨先生  -你他妈闭嘴  马丁
- Mr. Watts! - Shut the fuck up, Martin.
-沃茨先生  -我们都知道这个套路
- Mr. Watts. - We all know the drill.
你们会否决我的假释
You're going to deny my parole,
然后回家庆祝
then go home congratulating yourselves
自己又让这个世界安全了一点
on making the world a safer place.
但你们这些穷逼条子
But what you minimum wage pencil dicks
永远不能理解
can't possibly understand is
你们觉得我很讨厌
that however repulsive you seem to think I am,
但将要吞噬这整个国家
that the darkness swallowing this country whole
威胁你们和家里杂种们的黑暗
and coming for you and your half-breed families
远比我更恐怖
is a million fucking times worse.
就这样吧  沃茨先生
We're done here, Mr. Watts.
去你妈的  泰德
Go fuck yourself, Ted.
对了  谢里尔
Oh, and, Sheryl...
请你一定要
you be sure to give little
替她的雅利安叔叔  亲亲小绍莎娜·戈登
Shoshanna Golden a big kiss from her Aryan uncle
因为你知道  我肯定会想念她的
'cause you know I'm gonna be thinking about her.
只是精神上的痛苦
The pain is only psychological.
警长给你们五分钟时间
Sheriff's giving you five minutes.
你还是得来监狱看我吧
You finally get to visit me in jail, huh?
晚来总比不来好
Better late than never.
不是我干的
I didn't do this.
我知道
I know.
你觉得是谁干的
Do you have any idea who did?
还不清楚
Not yet.
不知道你想不想保释
I don't know if you'll make bail,
想的话  我可以抵押房子赎你出来
but I can use my house as collateral if you do.
谢谢
Thanks.
贾伯怎么样
How's Job?
他们把他折磨的够惨
They did a real number on him.
他会没事的
He'll be okay.
那你怎么办
How about you?
我真的想赶紧离开这
I really need to get the fuck out of here.
你好啊  泰德
Hello, Ted.
他怎么样
How is he?
他是无辜的  布罗克知道
Innocent and Brock knows it.
但有不利证据
Well, the evidence says
警长还得追查下去
otherwise and the sheriff has to follow up.
我要的东西拿到了吗
You got something for me?
拿到了
I did.
别着急
It can wait.
不  我需要转移注意力
No, I need the distraction.
这是毒品加工和分销机构
It's the details of a drug processing
的详细资料
and distribution facility.
-普罗科特的吗  -嗯哼
- Proctor's? - Mm-hmm.
谢谢你  邦克
Thank you, Bunker.
小心点  霍普韦尔夫人
Be careful, Mrs. Hopewell.
你被保释了
You just made bail.
我没有杀她
I didn't kill her.
或许是你杀的  或许不是  无所谓
Maybe you did, maybe you didn't. Either way.
这什么情况  给我滚开
What the hell is this? Get away from there!
普罗科特  你他妈的在干什么
Proctor, what the hell are you doing?
我把犯人保释了
I posted the prisoner's bail.
-保释  胡扯  -胡德要跟我走
- Bail? This is bullshit. - Hood is coming with me.
-他哪也不能去  -让他进来吧
- The hell he is. - Let him in.
-不  -别他妈挡我的路  布罗克
- No. - Get out of my way, Brock.
-别做梦了  -我可是他妈的市长
- Not gonna happen. - I'm the fucking mayor!
-但我是警长  -给我滚开
- And I'm the fucking sheriff! - Get out of the fucking way.
把钥匙给我  不然我就开枪了
You give me those keys or I will shoot you.
大家火气都好大啊
Everybody is so angry.
女士  你不该来这
Ma'am, you cannot be back here.
为什么  大家都在啊
Why not? Everybody else is.
邦克  请带这位女士出去
Bunker, take this woman up front, please.
等等  邦克
Stay put, Bunker.
我是特别探员维罗妮卡·道森
Special Agent Veronica Dawson.
暴力犯罪科的
Violent Crimes.
没错  一般人听完都会很震惊
Yeah, that always seems to suck the air right out of the room.
我知道你是警长洛特斯
I take it you're Sheriff Lotus.
这位是
And you are?
凯·普罗科特
Kai Proctor.
普罗科特先生  请节哀顺变
Mr. Proctor, I am truly sorry for your loss.
走吧  普罗科特
Let's go, Proctor.
-我来吧  -给我放开你的手
- I got this. - Get your fucking hands off me.
我来处理吧  警长
I got this, Sheriff.
普罗科特先生  我能想象
Mr. Proctor, I can only imagine
你处理这些事情的时候有多崩溃
how frustrated you must be with how things have been handled.
但这事现在由我接手
But this is my investigation now,
虽然我还没来得及补课
and while I've got a little bit of lost time to make up for,
但我向你保证会很快跟上
I can assure you I'm a quick study
我也会一查到底
and I plan to get to the bottom of things.
帮帮忙  给我点时间理清线索
Do me a favor, give me some time to sort things through,
一旦弄清了  我一定首先告诉你
and as soon as I do, you'll be the first to know.
给你二十四小时
You have 24 hours.
然后呢
Then what happens?
这群人真有意思
What a fun group.
你觉得她美吗
Do you think she's pretty?
我想他会很高兴
I think he'll be happy.
卢卡斯·胡德
Lucas Hood.
时任警长
Onetime sheriff.
闲时野人
Part-time mountain man.
现在是三起凶杀案的首要嫌犯
And now the primary suspect in three homicides.
经历真精彩
It's a hell of a resume.
洛特斯警长跟我说你话不多
Sheriff Lotus told me you don't talk much.
或许我只是对他话不多
Well, maybe I just don't talk to him much.
他也跟我说了凯莉副警长的事
He also told me about Deputy Kelly.
她死之前你们曾是一对
You two were a couple at the time of her death?
老天  一下子没了副警长和爱人
God, losing a deputy and a lover in one fell swoop.
肯定不好受
That must have been tough.
我有同感
I've been there.
我丈夫保罗
My husband Paul.
他当时带领着一支战术行动队
He was leading a tactical operation.
我们能顺着低层恐怖组织
Some low-level terrorist we could lean on
抓到更大的鱼
to get us some bigger fish.
按规矩  破门抓人
By the book, breach and arrest.
他按倒了罪犯  绑好了
He had the perp facedown and zip-tied
走的时候  那家伙13岁的侄子
when in walks the guy's 13-year-old nephew
拿着把格洛克9型手枪
holding a Glock 9.
保罗本可以立即击毙他
Paul could have dropped him in a heartbeat.
可是谁会向个孩子开枪
I mean, who can't outshoot a kid, right?
相反他想劝他投降
But instead he tried to talk him down.
我想那孩子不爱谈话
I guess that kid didn't feel like talking.
开枪打中保罗颈部
He shot Paul in the neck.
他当场毙命
Killed him instantly.
-你干这行有一阵了  -足够久
- You've been doing this a while. - Long enough.
那就该知道虚构丧夫的故事
Long enough to know that the fake husband story
骗不到像我这样的人
is not gonna work on someone like me.
你要么觉得我是傻逼
So either you think I'm an idiot
要么就想让我觉得你是
or you wanted me to call you on it.
目的是让我觉得有主导权吗
What, so that I would feel like I'm in control?
看来我们都知道那不可能
Seeing as we both know that's not true,
所以别废话了  想问什么就问吧
why don't you cut the bullshit and ask me what you want to ask?
好
Okay.
丽贝卡·鲍曼是你杀的吗
Did you kill Rebecca Bowman?
不是
No.
哟  答的好轻松
Well, that was easy.
很感谢你的配合  胡德先生
I so appreciate your cooperation, Mr. Hood.
不客气
You're welcome.
咱们还会再见的
I'm sure we'll meet again.
我想你在局里没多少朋友
I'm guessing you don't have a lot of pals down at the bureau.
你很了解联调局  对吧
You know a lot about the FBI, do you?
并没有
No, not really.
可瘾君子的样儿我倒是知道点
But I know a little something about burnouts.
我想你也知道
Yeah, I'll bet you do.
不是他干的
He didn't do it.
真的  才五分钟你就确定了
Really? You decided that in five minutes?
不  大概两分钟我就确定了
No, I decided that in about two.
证据...
The evidence--
证据没用  你也知道
The evidence is shit and you know it.
证据有用
The evidence isn't shit.
只是旁证
It's circumstantial.
那我把他放了
I'll cut him loose.
-别急  -为什么
- Not yet. - Why?
因为我们一放他走
Because the minute we release him,
胡德就会自己去找杀害鲍曼的凶手
Hood's gonna try to find Bowman's killer on his own.
我不想让他先找到
And I'd like a little bit of a head start.
顺便说一下
For the record,
我也知道你丈夫的事是在扯淡
I also knew that your husband story was bullshit.
你知道普罗科特
Did you know that Proctor
和你以前的帮派在做毒品生意吗
was in the drug business with your old crew?
你在说什么呢
What are you talking about?
他的仓库周围有很多新纳粹分子
There are neo-Nazis crawling all over his warehouse.
你怎么知道的
How do you know that?
我正在监视他们
I'm looking at them right now.
柯特  你知情吗
Kurt, did you know?
如果我知道  我会告诉你的
If I knew, I would have said something to you.
听着  我们先撤一步  把事情搞清楚
Look, we need to take a step back and figure things out.
这会改变很多事
This changes things.
对我来说不会
Not for me, it doesn't.
卡莉
Carrie.
卡
Carr--
四个月前
你为什么没告诉我
Why didn't you tell me?
我想给你一个惊喜
I wanted the new facility to be a surprise.
什么时候可以投产
When will it be operational?
这周末  也许更早
The end of this week, maybe a little sooner.
我们可以安排两班轮换  在第一月创造三倍产能
We can run double shifts, triple the output in the first month.
我会雇佣一位新工头去监管
I'll hire a new foreman to oversee--
丽贝卡  兄弟会来管理运营
Rebecca, the Brotherhood will be managing this operation.
什么
What?
-是的  -为什么
- Yeah. - Why?
由他们打理
They can provide the distance
我作为市长可以避嫌
and the insulation I require as mayor.
-应该是我的  -我知道
- This should be mine. - No, I know.
但你要相信我
But you have to trust me on this.
我有更大的计划留给你
I have something much bigger planned for you.
好吧  你的大计划
Yes, your big plan.
我什么都没得到
Meanwhile nothing is happening
你却把我们的生意给了纳粹份子
and you're handing over our business to Nazis?
我知道你会这样认为
I know that's how it looks to you,
但我保证这样对我们最好
but I promise this is what's best for us.
不  是对你最好而已
No, this is what's best for you.
你从来都只关心自己
And that's all you've ever really cared about.
希望你别再把我当小孩
I wish you'd stop treating me like a child.
你不这么幼稚  我就不会了
I will when you stop acting like one.
你像我这么大时  你已经在管事情了
When you were my age, you were already running things.
没人阻拦你
There was no one holding you back.
那时也没有人保护我
There was no one protecting me either.
我不需要你的保护
I don't need your protection.
你当然需要
Yes, you do!
这生意很危险
This is a dangerous business.
我他妈的就很危险
I'm fucking dangerous!
你根本不知我有多危险
You have no idea how dangerous I am.
外婆的本意是好的  宝贝
Grandma means well, honey.
我觉得她只是在担心你
I think she's just worried about you.
你只是需要给她机会
You're just gonna have to give her a chance.
哪怕你只是为麦克斯假装一下
Well, could you at least pretend for Max?
因为我需要你做个表率
'Cause I need you to set a good example, that's why.
宝贝  稍等
Honey, hold on.
贾伯
Job?
蒂法  我一会儿再打给你
Deva, I'm gonna call you right back.
-妈的  贾伯  -妈的
- Fuck, Job! - Fuck!
我差点射中你
I almost shot you.
我他妈被你吓死了
Imagine my fucking relief.
你不该下床的
You shouldn't even be out of bed.
你也不该把你的AK机枪
And you shouldn't be storing your AKs
放在"安·泰勒"旁边
next to your Ann Taylor.
美国服装品牌
你怎么进来的
How'd you get in there?
我他妈会开锁呗
It's a motherfucking tumbler.
你这里的火力足够开战了啊
You got enough firepower in here to start a war.
不是开战
Not start one.
而是做个了断
Just finish it.
阿门
Amen.
此处祷文是倒着念的
恶凶离脱们我救...
Evil from us deliver but...
...债的人了免...
...us against trespass...
...们我同如...
...who those forgive us as...
...上天在行同如  上地在...
...heaven in is it as Earth on...
...圣为名的你尊都人愿...
...name thy be hallowed...
...父的上天...
...heaven in art who...
...在们我
...Father our.
有约啊
Hot date?
你该去睡会儿了
You should really get some sleep.
那我就得闭上眼睛
That would require me closing my eyes.
恢复是需要时间的  贾伯
It's gonna take time, Job.
去他妈的  我和你一起去
Fuck this. I'm coming with you.
我觉得不妥
That's a bad idea.
是  这他妈的是最糟糕的主意
No, it's the worst motherfucking idea ever.
你不能来
You're not coming.
没人能再对我发号施令  你也一样
Not you or nobody get to tell me what to do anymore.
你不能把我一个人丢在这房子里
You are not leaving me in this motherfucking house alone.
别  别
Just don't-- don't--
别离开我
don't leave me.
你在车里待着
You're staying in the car.
你需要人支援你
You're gonna need someone to watch your back.
-你需要人...  -我是认真的
- You're gonna need somebody-- - I'm serious.
好吧
Fine.
收到你的信息了  怎么了
Got your message. What happened?
-喝一杯  -不是吧
- Have a drink. - Come on, man.
我放下所有的事过来  还以为你出事了
I dropped everything 'cause I thought you were in trouble here.
我得回普罗科特那儿去
Shit, I need to get back to Proctor's--
去他妈的普罗科特
Fuck Proctor.
给我坐下  他妈放尊重点儿
Now sit down and show me some goddamn respect.
不  不  别这么娘们
No, no, don't be a fucking pussy.
行吗
Okay?
好了
There you go.
喝吧
Drink.
你还好吧
You all right, man?
沃茨就不该和普罗科特做交易
Watts should have never made a deal with Proctor.
他只顾着
He's so busy
为自己退休以后着想
chasing his own retirement plan
所以他放弃了
that he's abandoned
我们这些年奋斗的一切
everything that we've been fighting for all these years.
他也许被普罗科特的钱冲昏了头脑
He may be blinded by Proctor's money,
但我没有
but I'm not.
而我也不再会缄口不言
And I'm not gonna keep my mouth shut anymore.
加尔文  兄弟  你醉了
Calvin, you're drunk, buddy.
-不管你打什么算盘  -不  不
- Whatever you're thinking-- - No. No.
我受够了考虑  乔
I'm done thinking, Joe.
我受够了当沃茨的跟班
I'm done being Watts' bitch.
我他妈现在该爷们起来了
It's time for me to man the fuck up.
沃茨必须滚蛋
Watts has to fucking go.
我们都耗了几个月了 贾伯
We've been at this for months, Job.
你一定厌烦了
You must be getting tired.
我们来调节一下气氛吧
Let's change the mood, shall we?
贾伯
Job.
Job. Job.
-你没事吧  -没事
- You okay? - I'm fine.
你呢
How about you?
我还好
I'm fine.
是啊  你看着他妈是挺好的
Yeah, you look fucking fine.
这时候别闹
Not now.
以防我真要独自开车回去
Just in case I do have to drive home alone,
你要给我说下做这事的目的吗
you want to tell me what this is really about?
为什么你要这么干
Why are you doing this?
你觉得搞"猫女"这一套
Do you think all this Catwoman bullshit
《蝙蝠侠》系列中喜欢冒险的大盗
是他想看到的吗
is what he would have wanted?
待在车里
Stay in the car.
他说了什么
Hey, what did he say?
他说你会挂掉
He said you're gonna die.
什么鬼
Oh, what the hell is this?
这里是私人场所
Hey, this is private property.
你他妈是谁
Who the fuck are you?
我问你话呢
I asked you a question.
你聋了吗  臭三八
Are you deaf, you stupid bitch?
没  我听得很清楚
No, I hear you loud and clear...
贱人
Bitch.
操
Shit!
快出来  贱人  快
Come on back, bitch. Come on.
贱人  贱人  快点  快点
Bitch-- bitch, move. Move!
进展如何
So how'd that go?
非常顺利
Like clockwork.
打开13号门
Unlock gate 13.
很快再见面哦  囚犯
See you again real soon there, convict.
操你妈  拉里
And you fuck your mama, Larry.
你来接我
You my ride?
车子不错  德国佬造的车最棒了
Nice car. Them Krauts always done it best.
我们是要去女妖镇吗
We headed to Banshee?
普罗科特先生想在你方便时尽早见你
Mr. Proctor would like to see you at your earliest convenience.
那还不快走
Well, then what the hell are we waiting for?
-操  -联调局  烂货们
- Fuck. - FBI, skeezy fuckers.
把烟管放下
Put the pipe down.
你干什么
What are you doing?
他妈给滚出去  滚
Get the fuck out of here. Go.
道森
Dawson.
这就去
On my way.
瑞文  这是联调局的道森探员
Raven, this is Agent Dawson from the FBI.
有什么发现
Yeah, what do we got?
法医根据尸体温度
Coroner estimated she was killed
和尸斑推断
nine or 10 hours ago
她大约在9或10小时前遇害
based on body temp and lividity.
-还是先前的作案手法吗  -对
- MO is the same? - Yeah.
漂亮女性  18到24岁
Attractive female, 18-24.
狗杂种也把她的心脏挖出来了
Son of a bitch cut her heart out, too.
切口非外科医生手法  不过很精确
Cut isn't surgical, but it is precise.
他切的时候是在一个安全地方
He's in a safe place when he does this.
有条不紊
Takes his time.
这是防卫伤口吗
Defensive wounds?
是捆绑痕迹
Ligature marks,
跟其他受害者一样
just like the other victims.
她被绑住了
She was tied up.
某种绳子  很粗很结实
Some kind of rope, heavy braiding.
足够造成这样的淤青
Enough to bruise like this?
她被捆绑了一段时间
She was bound for a while.
他不是马上杀死她们
He doesn't kill them right away.
没有性侵的迹象
No signs of sexual abuse.
不  他对她们没有性欲
No, he doesn't see them sexually.
这儿  他给她下药了
Right here. He drugged her.
和其他受害者一样
Just like the others.
活生生将她宰杀
Butchered her alive.
查到身份了吗
Got an ID?
还没有
No, nothing yet.
目击者证词呢
What'd the witness say?
早上5点之后  无意间看见有人
Caught a glimpse of someone dragging the body
在林子里拖尸体
into the woods just after 5:00 A.M.
那目击者为什么4个小时后才报案
And why the hell did they wait 4 hours to call it in?
因为他妈妈以为是他乱编的
Because his mommy thought he was making it up.
孩子叫什么
What's the kid's name?
-图科  -图科
- Tocho. - Tocho.
把她盖起来吧
Let's cover her up.
记得给角落处都做上标记
Make sure the coroner gets all those notes, yeah?
你叫图科吧  是你吧
Are you Tocho? Is that you?
你能和我说说你看到了什么吗
Can you-- can you tell me what you saw?
是男人还是女人
Was it a man or a woman, huh?
-年轻还是年老  -拜托  行了
- Young or old? - Come on, that's enough.
别再问了  走吧图科
No more questions, huh? Come on, Tocho.
我马上给你切好啦
Okay, I'm gonna finish cutting this for you
你要都吃掉哦
and you're gonna eat all of it.
-然后吃蛋糕  -好哒
- And then treats. - Okay.
还有蔬菜哦
But the vegetables, too.
-好吗  -好哒
- Okay? - Okay.
-说话算数  -好
- Promise? - Yeah.
土豆怎么样
How are the potatoes?
有点干
Dry.
不好意思  肯定是我弄过头了
I'm sorry. I must have overcooked them.
你坐着
Stay here.
我操
What the fuck?
见到你也很高兴  加尔文
It's nice to see you, too, Calvin.
没错  我也想进来
And, yes, I'd love to come inside.
我是闻到小玛吉做的菜了吗
Do I smell Magpie's cooking?
你怎么出来的
How did you get out?
很曲折
It's a hell of a story.
有机会我再和你说
Maybe I'll tell it to you sometime.
爸
Daddy.
-你出狱啦  -好消息吧宝贝
- You're out? - Good news, baby.
我被平反啦
I've been rehabilitated.
你是谁啊
And who might you be?
汉克  这是你姥爷
Uh, Hank, this is your grandfather.
叫爷爷就行  小甜心
You just call me Papa, sweetheart.
好吧  我们要上楼去洗澡了
Uh, okay, we're gonna go up and take a bath now.
知道吗  男人心不靠谱
You know what? Fuck a man's heart.
想得到爱
You want love,
抓住他的胃就行
go right to his stomach.
恭喜
Congratulations.
你不是连环杀手
You're not a serial killer.
我需要你填几张表
I'll need you to fill out some paperwork.
四个月前
要载你一程吗
Need a ride?
你不像是怀恨在心的小心眼儿啊
You don't seem like the type to hold a grudge.
你不让我出狱
You kept me locked up.
我刚来
I just got here.
要立威
Had to get my bearings.
很高兴我能帮上忙
I'm glad I could help.
你知道我是无辜的
You knew I was innocent.
无辜有点夸张了吧  你觉得呢
I think innocent might be a bit of a stretch, don't you?
呵呵  操你妈
Yeah, fuck you.
嘿  我替你求的情  不用客气
Hey, you're welcome for that alibi, by the way.
听着  胡德  我知道你住哪
Look, Hood, I know where you live.
要走好远才能到你的小屋
It's a long walk to that cabin of yours.
我需要喝一杯
I need a drink.
你肯定也需要
You definitely need a drink.